<!--
  ~ Copyright (C) 2023 The Android Open Source Project
  ~
  ~ Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
  ~ you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
  ~ You may obtain a copy of the License at
  ~
  ~     https://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0
  ~
  ~ Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
  ~ distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
  ~ WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
  ~ See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
  ~ limitations under the License.
  -->
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Books</string>
    <string name="affirmation1">Dune (1968)</string>
    <string name="affirmation2">Babel (2022)</string>
    <string name="affirmation3">Percy Jackson (2005)</string>
    <string name="affirmation4">Lord of the rings (1988)</string>
    <string name="affirmation5">A scatter of Light (2023)</string>
    <string name="affirmation6">Mistborn #1 (2006)</string>
    <string name="affirmation7">The Witcher (1986)</string>
    <string name="affirmation8">The Blighted Stars (2023)</string>
    <string name="affirmation9">Intermezzo (2024)</string>
    <string name="affirmation10">Starter Villain (2023)</string>

    <string name="desc1">One of the pivotal works of literary science fiction, Frank Herbert’s sand-blasted epic details the internecine battles for control of the desert planet Arrakis and its precious resource, \'spice\'.</string>
    <string name="desc2">One of the leading lights in the visceral grimdark fantasy genre, Kuang\'s stunningly wrought novel is a compulsive dystopia about the power of language and the evils of authoritarianism, represented by the looming titular tower of translation.</string>
    <string name="desc3">The first adventure for Percy Jackson sets the reluctant hero a ten-day deadline to find the true snatcher of Zeus\' legendary lightning bolt in Riordan\'s page-turning, myth-packed tale.</string>
    <string name="desc4">The first part of Tolkien\'s genre-defining masterpiece introduces arguably the most famous quest in fiction, as Frodo and his comrades set off to destroy the One Ring.</string>
    <string name="desc5">Scatter of Light is a companion novel to the National Book Awards winner and New York Times bestseller Last Night at the Telegraph Club, and is about how the threads of family, inspiration, art, and identity are woven across generations.</string>
    <string name="desc6">Kickstarting the Mistborn series in stunning style, Sanderson\'s wildly entertaining fantasy heist sees a motley assortment of criminals attempt to overthrow an all-powerful tyrant.</string>
    <string name="desc7">Introducing Geralt the Witcher - revered and hated - who holds the line against the monsters plaguing humanity in the bestselling series that inspired the Witcher video games and a major Netflix show.</string>
    <string name="desc8">When a spy and her mortal enemy crash-land on a dying planet, she must figure out how to survive long enough to uncover the deadly, galaxy-spanning conspiracy that landed them there. The Blighted Stars is the first book in an epic new space-opera trilogy from the author of the Philip K. Dick-nominated Velocity Weapon.</string>
    <string name="desc9">Two brothers navigate the turmoil and joy of love after the passing of their father in this breathtaking novel from the hugely acclaimed author of Normal People and Conversations With Friends.</string>
    <string name="desc10">A hiss-terical story about the (un)luckiest nepo-baby of all time, Starter Villain follows an everyman who inherits his uncle\'s supervillain empire.</string>



</resources>
